I was home alone and scared out of my PLURAL_NOUN.
I could hear the wind VERB_ENDING_IN_ING, and off in the distance a/an NOUN was howling.
I crossed the room, locked the NOUN and climbed into bed, pulling the PLURAL_NOUN over my PART_OF_THE_BODY.	
Then it happened. I could hear a/an NOUN VERB_ENDING_IN_ING up the stairs.	
My PART_OF_THE_BODY_PLURAL started to chatter and my knees began VERB_ENDING_IN_ING.
The NOUN was thrust open and there was a huge NOUN with hair all over his PART_OF_THE_BODY.	
It was my father. 
"Hi, we're home," he said ADVERB.
"Hope you weren't afraid of staying home alone."
"No," I said, lying through my PART_OF_THE_BODY_PLURAL.
