American children are fascinated by ADJECTIVE stuff—like stories that scare the PLURAL_NOUN off them or make their PLURAL_NOUN stand on end. 
Scientists say this is because being frightened causes the SILLY_WORD gland to function and puts TYPE_OF_LIQUID	into their blood. 
And everyone knows that makes kids feel ADJECTIVE.
When they are scared by a movie or a/an	NOUN, some kids laugh and holler and VERB. 
Others cover their eyes with their PLURAL_NOUN and keep screaming and VERB_ENDING_IN_ING. 
Most kids get over this by the time they are NUMBER years old.
Then they like movies about cars VERB_ENDING_IN_ING or cops shooting PLURAL NOUN, or they like movies about a teenager meeting a/an NOUN and falling in love.
Of course, that can be scary, too.
