Ye can always pretend to be a bloodthirsty NOUN, threatening everyone by waving yer ADJECTIVE sword in the air, but until ye learn to VERB like a pirate, ye'll never be ADVERB accepted as an authentic NOUN.
So here's what ye do: Cleverly work into yer daily conversations ADJECTIVE pirate phrases such as "Ahoy there, PLURAL_NOUN," "Avast, ye PLURAL_NOUN," and "Shiver me PLURAL_NOUN."
Remember to drop all yer gs when ye say such words as salin', spittin', and fightin'.This will givc ye a/an PART_OF_THE_BODY start to being recognized as a swashbucklin' NOUN.	
Once ye have the lingo down pat, it helps to wear a three-cornered NOUN	on yer head, stash a/an NOUN in yer pants, and keep a/an NOUN perched atop yer PART_OF_THE_BODY. 
Aye, now ye be a real pirate!